a11news.com 2009-12-15

# Privacy Policy

**A11News.com Privacy Policy**  
The following privacy statement covers the A11News.com website. Please read this statement regarding our website. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

Ownership of Information  
A11News.com is the sole owner of the information collected on the A11News.com website.

Comments  
In order to enhance their use of the A11News.com website, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. A11News.com will screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use.

Mailing List  
A11News.com may launch a mailing list at some time in the future. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

Public Forums  
This site makes public comments, chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Third Party Cookies  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, A11News.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by A11News.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Third Party Advertising  
The ads appearing on the A11News.com website are delivered to users by third party advertisers including Google, among others. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx):

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on A11News.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to A11News.com and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**LIMIT USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION** – You can limit the use of any personal information in several ways. First, do not signup for the forum or our newsletter. If you unsubscribe from the newsletter, your information and email address are deleted from all our files. If you delete your forum profile, all your personal information is removed from our forum database. If you need assistance with removal of your personal information, please contact us.

Log Files  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, A11News.com may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on the A11News.com website.

Business Transitions  
In the event A11News.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

Links  
The A11News.com website contain links to other sites. Please be aware that A11News.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by A11News.com.

Notification of Changes  
Whenever A11News.com changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

Contact Information  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using the comment form on any page of the website.

Tags: [cookies](http://a11news.com/tag/cookies/ "cookies"), [disclaimer](http://a11news.com/tag/disclaimer/ "disclaimer"), [fine print](http://a11news.com/tag/fine-print/ "fine print"), [privacy policy](http://a11news.com/tag/privacy-policy/ "privacy policy")

#### Related posts
